Jacob Moore

Work Statement

I am a software developer with experience in Java, C#, shell scripting, refactoring legacy code, and Linux.

I want to write and ship good code as an important part of a dev team. I want to lead sprints, increase test coverage, improve documentation, and streamline internal processes.

Work Experience

SNT Media, Wichita, KS Information Architect: 2016/09 - 2017/05

- Create, design, and execute content strategy for new content verticals with Natural Language Generation.
- Write and maintain technical documentation for internal tools.

Applianz Technologies, Wichita, KS Junior Developer: 2015/01 - 2016/09

- Spec, write, and undergo review for tasks assigned by Lead Dev, using bug reports, logging, and testing to guide process.
- Interpret, dissect, and resolve Support escalations.
- Deploy and maintain code for >300 local and remote systems.
- Refactor and improve legacy code whenever it is touched.

Support Coordinator: 2014/03 - 2014/12

- Use problem solving, troubleshooting, and shell scripting to improve client outcomes.
- Submit detailed bug reports.
- Promoted to Developer in January 2015.

Education

Butler Community College Andover, KS, 2009-2011 English Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/jacobmmoore

Personal: jacobmoore.cool Twitter: @jmmoore_

Email: jacob@moorejm.com

Phone: 316.734.0026

Accomplishments

Re-engineered backup process for entire fleet leading to smaller, faster backups and vastly simplified disaster recovery.

Wrote deployment playbooks in Ansible for internal tools and fleet config management, lowering bus factor and creating repeatable, usable deployments.

Contributed heavily to new employee training with documentation and easy to follow guides for more complex repair processes.

Proofread/copyedited marketing materials, official communications, internal wiki articles, how-to guides for technicians, and acted as an all-around word guru.

Projects/Hobbies

Kansas Linux Fest May 13-14, 2017 Volunteer

devICT Java Talk Kotlin: From Russia with... Nice Syntax August 16, 2016

Hackathon ICT June 4-5, 2016 Volunteer

Hero Complex Cube League November 2013 - Present Organizer